mynavyexchange.com 2019-05-08

# Nexcom Privacy Policy | Shop Your Navy Exchange - Official Site

Home / NEXCOM Enterprise Privacy Statement

Notice: This is a U.S. Government Web Site

CUSTOMERS

This is a World Wide Web site for official information about Navy Exchange Service Command. It is provided as a public service by Navy Exchange Service Command. The purpose is to provide information and news about the Navy Exchange Service Command to the general public. All information on this site is public domain and may be distributed or copied unless otherwise specified. Use of appropriate byline/photo/image credits is requested. Unauthorized attempts to upload information or change information on this Web site are strictly prohibited and may be punishable under the Computer Fraud and Abuse Act of 1986 and the National Information Infrastructure Protection Act. For site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all users, this government computer system employs software programs to monitor network traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage.

Except for authorized law enforcement investigation and to maintain required correspondence files, no other attempts are made to identify individual users or their usage habits. Raw data logs are used to simply determine how many users are accessing the site, which pages are the most popular, and, from time to time, from which top level domain users are coming. This data is scheduled for regular destruction in accordance with National Archives and Records Administration guidelines.

Web measurement and customization technologies (WMCT) may be used on this site to remember your online interactions, to conduct measurement and analysis of usage, or to customize your experience. The Department of Defense does not use the information associated with WMCT to track individual user activity on the Internet outside of Defense Department websites, nor does it share the data obtained through such technologies, without your explicit consent, with other departments or agencies. The Department of Defense does not keep a database of information obtained from the use of WMCT. General instructions for how you may opt out of some of the most commonly used WMCT is available at <http://www.usa.gov/optout_instructions.shtml>.

By sending us an electronic mail message (for example, an e-mail message addressed to the webmaster), you may be sending us personally-identifying information. In these cases, we may retain the information as long as necessary to respond to your request or otherwise resolve the subject matter of your e-mail. Please be aware that e-mail is not necessarily secure from interception or misdirection. For your own protection you may wish to communicate sensitive information using a method other than e-mail.

We do not rent, sell, or exchange your name with other organizations. We protect our databases with various physical, technical and procedural measures and we restrict access to your information by unauthorized persons. Our information systems are maintained behind a software firewall to isolate them from access by other networks connected to the internet.

All information transmitted through our website is stored on our secure server. We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology, which is the electronic commerce standard for securing information over the internet. SSL technology encrypts your information, preventing an unauthorized party from viewing and downloading your information. Your web browser should display a web address with an “https” prefix, indicating that the SSL technology is operating when using our website.

You may access online sale flyers or sign up to receive promotional correspondence from the Navy Exchange. You can also choose at any time to discontinue receiving such correspondence. You can tell us to stop sending correspondence by clicking on the Sale Flyer section. Further, each promotional email we send contains a link that allows you to discontinue future emails from us. If you have questions or comments, you may contact us by email by clicking on the Contact Us section. You may also call or write us at the address & phone number below.

Navy Exchange Service Command

Customer Service

3280 Virginia Beach Blvd.

Virginia Beach, VA 23452

Toll free: 1-800-628-3924 (9:00AM-4:00PM, Monday-Friday, except Federal holidays)  
  
---  

VENDORS

There have been recent incidents of personal data loss involving both government and commercial entities. Accordingly, the Department of Defense (DoD) and the Department of the Navy (DoN) have taken action to mitigate these losses, such as training all DoD and DoN personnel on basic DoD Privacy Act compliance requirements. Recently, DoD and DoN have added the requirement that all who do business with DoD and DoN (including all contractors and vendors) understand that:

  *  The collection of personal data is limited under the Privacy Act (5 U.S.C. 552A) to information relevant and necessary to accomplish a DoD/DoN purpose set forth in Law or regulation, and that dissemination of personal data except with consent of individual involved is prohibited;
  * The willful disclosure of personal information, unless authorized by applicable law or regulation, is subject to criminal prosecution; and;

  * Contractors/vendors and their employees are stewards of personal information in their possession and that they have an affirmative responsibility to ensure personal information is collected, maintained, used, and disseminated only as allowed by applicable law or regulation, and for continually safeguarding such information (i.e., treating and protecting as if their own).
  * All contractors who have potential access to PII must also complete the PII training and have a record of completion on file. Contractors are subject to the same provisions as Federal employees and military members under the Privacy Act.

A business partner (contractor, vendor, and all employees, representatives, subcontractors, etc.), that conducts official business in any capacity with NEXCOM involving receiving or obtaining information subject to safeguarding requirements of the Privacy Act, shall ensure full compliance with the Privacy Act at all times. For additional guidance, see the DoN Chief Information Officer website   <<http://www.doncio.navy.mil/ContentView.aspx?ID=1876>>.  
  
Notice: This is a U.S. Government Web Site

This is a World Wide Web site for official information about Navy Exchange Service Command. It is provided as a public service by Navy Exchange Service Command. The purpose is to provide information and news about the Navy Exchange Service Command to the general public. All information on this site is public domain and may be distributed or copied unless otherwise specified. Use of appropriate byline/photo/image credits is requested. Unauthorized attempts to upload information or change information on this Web site are strictly prohibited and may be punishable under the Computer Fraud and Abuse Act of 1986 and the National Information Infrastructure Protection Act. For site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all users, this government computer system employs software programs to monitor network traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage.

Except for authorized law enforcement investigation and to maintain required correspondence files, no other attempts are made to identify individual users or their usage habits. Raw data logs are used to simply determine how many users are accessing the site, which pages are the most popular, and, from time to time, from which top level domain users are coming. This data is scheduled for regular destruction in accordance with National Archives and Records Administration guidelines.

Web measurement and customization technologies (WMCT) may be used on this site to remember your online interactions, to conduct measurement and analysis of usage, or to customize your experience. The Department of Defense does not use the information associated with WMCT to track individual user activity on the Internet outside of Defense Department websites, nor does it share the data obtained through such technologies, without your explicit consent, with other departments or agencies. The Department of Defense does not keep a database of information obtained from the use of WMCT. General instructions for how you may opt out of some of the most commonly used WMCT is available at http://www.usa.gov/optout_instructions.shtml.

By sending us an electronic mail message (for example, an e-mail message addressed to the webmaster), you may be sending us personally-identifying information. In these cases, we may retain the information as long as necessary to respond to your request or otherwise resolve the subject matter of your e-mail. Please be aware that e-mail is not necessarily secure from interception or misdirection. For your own protection you may wish to communicate sensitive information using a method other than e-mail.

We do not rent, sell, or exchange your name with other organizations. We protect our databases with various physical, technical and procedural measures and we restrict access to your information by unauthorized persons. Our information systems are maintained behind a software firewall to isolate them from access by other networks connected to the internet.

All information transmitted through our website is stored on our secure server. We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology, which is the electronic commerce standard for securing information over the internet. SSL technology encrypts your information, preventing an unauthorized party from viewing and downloading your information. Your web browser should display a web address with an “https” prefix, indicating that the SSL technology is operating when using our website.

You may access online sale flyers or sign up to receive promotional correspondence from the Navy Exchange. You can also choose at any time to discontinue receiving such correspondence. You can tell us to stop sending correspondence by clicking on the Sale Flyer section. Further, each promotional email we send contains a link that allows you to discontinue future emails from us. If you have questions or comments, you may contact us by email by clicking on the Contact Us section. You may also call or write us at the address & phone number below.

Navy Exchange Service Command  
Customer Service  
3280 Virginia Beach Blvd.  
Virginia Beach, VA 23452

Toll free: 1-800-628-3924 (9:00AM-4:00PM, Monday-Friday, except Federal holidays)

VENDORS

There have been recent incidents of personal data loss involving both government and commercial entities. Accordingly, the Department of Defense (DoD) and the Department of the Navy (DoN) have taken action to mitigate these losses, such as training all DoD and DoN personnel on basic DoD Privacy Act compliance requirements. Recently, DoD and DoN have added the requirement that all who do business with DoD and DoN (including all contractors and vendors) understand that:

  * The collection of personal data is limited under the Privacy Act (5 U.S.C. 552A) to information relevant and necessary to accomplish a DoD/DoN purpose set forth in Law or regulation, and that dissemination of personal data except with consent of individual involved is prohibited;
  * The willful disclosure of personal information, unless authorized by applicable law or regulation, is subject to criminal prosecution; and;
  * Contractors/vendors and their employees are stewards of personal information in their possession and that they have an affirmative responsibility to ensure personal information is collected, maintained, used, and disseminated only as allowed by applicable law or regulation, and for continually safeguarding such information (i.e., treating and protecting as if their own).
  * All contractors who have potential access to PII must also complete the PII training and have a record of completion on file. Contractors are subject to the same provisions as Federal employees and military members under the Privacy Act.

A business partner (contractor, vendor, and all employees, representatives, subcontractors, etc.), that conducts official business in any capacity with NEXCOM involving receiving or obtaining information subject to safeguarding requirements of the Privacy Act, shall ensure full compliance with the Privacy Act at all times. For additional guidance, see the DoN Chief Information Officer website [here](http://www.doncio.navy.mil/ContentView.aspx?ID=1876).
